I have to make this video stop putting
suffixes on your shell scripts on Linux
Mac and Unix just stop there's no reason
for it you're breaking the world of sh
scripting and you're doing it wrong and
if you don't like it fight me put put it
in the comments give me your reasons for
adding Dosh to the end of your
entrypoint.sh
script why would you do
this seriously I'm asking you a very
serious question put it in the comments
below if you can figure out a reason to
justify to make it so that your shell
script cannot be changed into any other
language ever I want to know because
that's what you just did by putting Dosh
at the end of that you have now to
ensure that that unix's executable can't
be changed to python or Pearl or any
other language it can't be replaced with
a binary and go it can't be you have now
rendered that executable completely
incompatible with any possible future
version or preacher language you might
want to put it in why why did you do
that why did you do that if you have a
good reason to do that tell me because I
have never seen a good reason the only
reason I've ever heard people say to do
this is in the very extreme Edge case of
python with py which will not work it's
because more about python being broken
or are people using Windows and they're
saying well Windows require suffixes for
everything it certainly doesn't require
a sh
file Windows might require a py file for
python it's one of the reasons python is
so broken in so many ways look I I use
Python people use it for lots of things
don't get mad at me I love anible but
this this extension crap has got to stop
stop putting extensions on your
executables you are shoehorning you're
you're forcing your self to always use a
shell scrap by the way I've seen people
put bash at the end and people put sh at
the end and people do put all kinds of
crap at the end don't do it just make it
without a suffix it doesn't need a
suffix plus now we all have to type a
suff well I just T compl it doesn't
matter it's just ugly don't do it fite
me